Andrew Simons

512-944-9351

Simdrew07@gmail.com

I am a dedicated and driven Operations Manager with over five years of experience providing team guidance, training, and technical support to my company. I am seeking a position that will showcase and strengthen my strong work-ethic, creative thinking, business acumen and multi-tasking abilities. My goal is to advance my career with a progressive, innovative company and add value to process execution and expand my business skills.

Skills

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React, Node, Git, Express, Redux, RestAPI, MySQL, Node.js, jQuery, Bootstrap
Expertise and knowledge in business operations protocol
Policy oversight and and adherence monitoring
Proficient in Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Centerbase, Sugar CRM

Education

Delta State University (August 2007- May 2011) B.A. in Business Management (Cleveland, MS)

Experience

Operations Manager, 360 Home Connect (October 2017 – present)

- Run day to day operations for sales and order support teams
- Coordinate and lead weekly meetings with sales and QA departments
- Weekly leadership meetings with department heads
- Weekly order support meetings with provider portals and sugar CRM
- Sugar CRM training with sales consultants
- Resolve sales consultant business operational issues
- Interview and hire candidates for order support and sales consultant positions
- Quarterly performance reviews of order support team members
- Oversee order support task lists and ensure tasks are submitted through correct partner portals
- Train teams on Sugar CRM system which stores client and sales information for utility services
- Navigate and operate OPUS AT&T system to schedule orders and monitor installations
- Collect monthly reports of sales through OPUS to Sugar CRM
- Update business rules and automation processes
- Maintain vendor relationships and contracts- negotiate contracts with vendor partners to sell products at competitive rates

• Update sales and order teams with vendor marketing promotions

Order Support, 360 Home Connect (May 2016- October 2017)

- Reviewing and submitting orders for partner companies
- Schedule installations and activations
- Client follow-up to ensure services are operating correctly
- Customer service and complaint resolution

Austin Golf Club, Assistant Professional (4/2015 – 5/2016)

- Service oriented work involving operations and scheduling
- o Driving range management
- Equipment management scheduling, operation, and inventory

Certifications

Austin Coding Academy (9/2019 – 8/2020)

- Built HTML and CSS applications
- o Backend (MySQL, Express, Firebase, RestAPI)
- Specialize in Javascript and React to build full-stack web applications

Projects

Developed pricing calculator app designed to assist sales consultants. This web application provides the latest prices and promotions for all utility providers in one place rather than consultants having to use multiple pricing resources. This streamlines daily operations as consultants can work more independently.

https://price-calculator-26fca.web.app

Connect Four game application https://connectfour-2c513.web.app/